Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University President's Office records
1962-1968
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. President
C304
185 cubic feet 185 boxes
The first president of what was then Indiana College was elected by the Board of Trustees in 1829. Elvis J. Stahr, Jr. served as president of Indiana University from 1962-1968. Collection consists of records created or collected by the Indiana University Office of the President during Elvis Stahr's tenure, and includes correspondence, studies, and reports documenting the various administrative processes, committees, events and university departments and schools during this period.
Access Restrictions
Select files are closed to researchers. These are indicated in the finding aid.
Advance notice required for access.
Biographical Note
Elvis J. Stahr, Jr., was born in Hickman, Kentucky on March 9, 1916 to Elvis Jacob and Mary Anne (McDaniel) Stahr. After graduating high school as valedictorian in 1932 at the age of sixteen, he attended the University of Kentucky where he was a member of the Sigma Chi fraternity, the ROTC program, and the varsity tennis and debate teams. He graduated in 1936 with a degree in English Literature and the highest grades on record at the University of Kentucky. He continued his education at the University of Oxford in England as a Rhodes Scholar, where he received a B.A. in jurisprudence and a B.A. in civil law in 1938 and 1939, respectively. Later, he received his M.A. from Oxford in 1943.
After his graduation from Oxford, Stahr practiced law as an associate in the New York firm Mudge, Stern, Baldwin, and Tucker from July 1939 to February 1941. However, his law practice was interrupted by World War II. Stahr joined the war effort in October 1941 as a second lieutenant and served for twenty-six months overseas, mainly in China, but also in India and North Africa. During his military tour, he received the Special Breast Order of Yun Hui, twice awarded by the Nationalist Republic of China, and the Bronze Star medal with Oak Leaf Cluster, among other honors. He ended his stint in the Army as a lieutenant colonel. During his tenure as an officer of the United States Army, he received a diploma in Chinese language in 1943 from Yale University.
Dr. Stahr left the Army in 1946 and again joined the law firm of Mudge, Stern, Williams, and Tucker, this time as a senior associate, but left in 1947 to return to what he called his first love, higher education. He joined the faculty of his alma mater, the University of Kentucky, as an associate professor of law in 1947, but was quickly promoted to full time faculty in 1948, and soon thereafter, to the position of Dean of the College of Law. He was the youngest, (at the age of 32) to serve in this post. In 1954, he was named Provost of the University of Kentucky. During his career at the University of Kentucky, he also served as special assistant to the Secretary of the Army during the Korean Conflict, and under United States President Dwight D. Eisenhower in1956 as the executive director of the Committee on Education beyond High School. He left the University of Kentucky in 1957 to become the Vice Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh. Soon after, he left his position at the University of Pittsburgh to become the President of the University of West Virginia. He stayed in West Virginia for two years before accepting the nomination by President Kennedy to serve as the Secretary of the Army. While in this position, Stahr established the Army Intelligence and Security Branch as a separate, professional division of the Army, oversaw the reorganization of the combat division of the Army, and expanded the community relations of the Army.
Stahr gave up the position of Secretary of the Army to return to higher education as the President of Indiana University in 1962, where he succeeded his friend Herman B Wells as Indiana University's 12th President. In his inaugural address, he stressed the need for maintaining the leadership role IU had in fields where it was nationally renowned, for spending Indiana tax dollars to prepare the campus for the expected large influx of baby boom generation students, and for stressing the importance of higher education in creating jobs and security in the state of Indiana.
During Stahr's presidency, Indiana University saw its largest expansion. In the course of his term, the awarding of baccalaureate degrees at the regional campuses began, as well as the addition of majors, such as the Study of Religion; of Divisions, such as the Honors Division, and of Schools, such as the Library Science School, within the Bloomington campus. He guided plans for the building of Assembly Hall, the Student Health Center, the Optometry Building, the Graduate Residence Center, and several different residence halls, including Briscoe, Wilkie, and Forest. The University School was also built during his term. His presidency witnessed the creation of the Aerospace Research Center which acted as a clearinghouse for technology developed by the government to be adapted for civilian use. His tenure also saw a large growth in the number of students and faculty, not only in Bloomington, but also in the regional campuses. Finally, Stahr led a reorganization of the university administration into three separate and distinct areas, the Bloomington campus led by a chancellor, the Indianapolis campus, and the regional campuses as more autonomous units.
Dr. Stahr served as Indiana University President until 1968 when he stepped down due to "presidential fatigue." He wrote to the Board of Trustees stating that although he had enjoyed his term as president, he felt that he could no longer devote himself to such a large task as president. His intention, he told the Board of Trustees, was to return to Indiana University after a sabbatical as a professor of law. However, he accepted the position as President of the National Audubon Society in 1968, writing that the issue of conservation was something that could not be ignored. He retired as President of the National Audubon Society in 1978, after having seen the membership rate almost quadruple to 400,000, and being instrumental in liberalizing the tax laws in the United States to allow charitable organizations to lobby on public policy issues. Although retired, he was still active in a number of environmental and public service organizations until his death of cancer on November 11, 1998.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by subject. Within subject headings, items are arranged chronologically or alphabetically by title as required.
Scope and Content Note
The general file folders mostly contain the correspondence of President Stahr and Joseph Ewers, Assistant to the President. Prominent topics within this correspondence include pay raises for faculty members, complaints registered to the president, and requests for scholastic information. Topical areas with significant amounts of material include the Assembly Hall controversy and construction, the Nigerian Project, the founding of WTIU (located under Radio and Television), Indiana state matters encompassing university relations with Congress and the State Legislature, the civil rights movement in education (found under the original 1960's heading 'negro'), the Indiana University self-study conducted over a period of three years, speakers Herbert Aptheker and Allen Ginsburg with the ensuing controversy, Vietnam War and related student protests, and the Young Socialist Alliance controversy. The collection also includes materials relating to members of the Indiana University community, including Dean Wilfred C. Bain, Ralph Collins, George H. List, Joseph Sutton, and Herman B Wells. Similar records may be found related to prominent politicians and researchers such as Governor Birch Bayh, United States vice president Hebert H. Humphrey, Francis Keppel, and Indiana Governor Matthew E. Walsh.
The records in this collection represent the bulk of the records from Elvis Stahr's tenure as president of IU. However, additions may be made to these records periodically as they are found in other accessions. Please ask Archives staff for more details.
Separated Material
Three photographs were pulled: Archives, 1962-1968, photos of Robert W. Frey Bau general, 1966-1968, photo of Ted Allen Baumgartner California, University of, 1966-1968, photo of men cleaning a statute with graffiti.
Acquisition Information
Accession 0087
Appraisal
Folders in box 185 beginning with International Center Administration board minutes were originally part of collection 48. Initially interspersed throughout the Elvis J. Stahr collection, these items were moved to the end of the collection and re-labeled with the appropriate collection number.
President's Office payroll and personnel files were destroyed in March 2022 in accordance with university record retention and disposition policies (originally in Box 129).
College presidents--Indiana--Archives.; College presidents--Indiana--Correspondence.; Universities and colleges--Indiana--Administration.; Indiana University. President -- Archives; Indiana University. President -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Indiana University -- Administration; Stahr, Elvis J. (Elvis Jacob), 1916-1998 -- Archives; Stahr, Elvis J. (Elvis Jacob), 1916-1998 -- Correspondence
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - General file index, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - A, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 1)
  - Abr, general, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 1)
  - Abstine, James, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Academic freedom, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Academic freedom-Wisconsin alumnus, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Academic garb, 1963-1966; (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Accelerator (low energy) budget study 100 MEV Cyclotron facility Indiana University (Brobeck & Assoc.), 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Accounting department (Box 1)
    - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - Annual report, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Accrediting agencies and accrediting, miscellaneous, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 1)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1963-1968 (Box 1)
  - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 2)
    - Report, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
    - 1962-1968, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Ad, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 2)
  - Administrative, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Administrative committee (Box 2)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 2)
    - 1957-1964 (Box 2)
    - Minutes, President Stahr's copies, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
  - Administrative committee (Box 3)
    - Minutes, complete file, 1962-1965 (Box 3)
    - Minutes, President Stahr's copies, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 3)
  - Administrative manual, 1960-1968 (Box 3)
  - Administrative procedures, 18 Jan. 1968 (Box 3)
  - Admission count, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Admission inquiries, Jun. 1963 (Box 3)
  - Admissions, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 3)
  - Admissions policy, adopted by Board of Trustees, June 4, 1960; Feb.-Aug. 1960 (Box 3)
  - Admissions-out of state students (Box 3)
    - Sept.-Dec. 1965 (Box 3)
    - Dec. 1963 (Box 3)
  - Adult Education (Box 3)
    - 1958-1967, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - Advanced and postdoctoral program annual report, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Aeons, Board of, 1962-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 3)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 3)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 3)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - ARAC minutes, 1962-1967 (Box 3)
  - Aerospace Medical Association, the Louis H. Bauer Lecture, Dunes Hotel, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Aerospace Research Applications Center (ARAC) (Box 4)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 4)
    - Indiana executive program conference, Apr. 8-9, 1965; Jan.-Apr. 1965 (Box 4)
    - Research and development campus, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - ARAC and economic growth, 1963-1966 (Box 4)
  - Afghanistan-A.I.D. program, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Afghanistan budget, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Afghanistan correspondence, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Africa, "Emerging Africa in the light of its past," manuals for A-V program, 1964 (Box 5)
  - African studies program (Box 5)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 5)
    - Annual report (Box 5)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 5)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 5)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 5)
  - Ag, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Agency for International Development, 1961-1963; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Air transportation department, 1966-1968 (Box 5)
  - Al, general, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Ale, general, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - All, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Allen, Dotaline, Jun. 1964-May 1965 (Box 5)
  - Alli, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Alumni-Stahr, (American Alumni Council), Dec. 1967 (Box 5)
  - Indiana University Alumni Association (Box 5)
    - Annual report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Alumni barbeque speech, commencement, 21 Jun. 1965 (Box 5)
    - IU Alumni Club of Grant County, Meshingomesia country club, Marion, Ind., Oct. 1966-Apr. 1967 (Box 5)
    - Alumni Council and Alumni, miscellaneous, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Regional campuses, Feb.-Apr. 1968 (Box 5)
    - DASA, Feb.-Jul. 1968 (Box 5)
    - Alumni Council and Alumni, miscellaneous, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Indiana University Alumni Association (Box 6)
    - Alumni Council and Alumni, miscellaneous, 1962-1968 (Box 6)
    - Distinguished Alumni Service Award, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - Am, general, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 6)
  - American, miscellaneous, A-Z, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - American Association of University Professors, Ballantine Hall, Sep.-Oct. 1965 (Box 6)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - American Council on Education (Box 6)
    - 1962-1969, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - American Council on Education (Box 7)
    - 1963-1966, (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - Expanding Opportunities Bulletin, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1962-1968 (Box 7)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      - Bulletin (Box 7)
        - 1962-1967, (6 folders) (Box 7)
        - Treasurer's Office Copies, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 7)
        - Mailing list, Oct. 1962-Feb. 1964 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education (Box 8)
    - Press Coverage of the 48th Annual Meeting, Oct 6-8, 1965; Sep.-Oct. 1965 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Publications List, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - Publications, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Jul. 1962-Jun. 1963 (Box 8)
    - Academic Administration Internship Program, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - Information for Tenth Edition of American Universities & Colleges, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Circulation Lists for ACE material, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Bulletins, Miscellaneous, 1964; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Commission on Federal Relations, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - American Council on Education (Box 9)
    - Commission on Federal Relations, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Commission on International Education, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Commission on Education and International Affairs, Apr.-Jun. 1963 (Box 9)
    - Committee on Equality of Educational Opportunity (Box 9)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 9)
        - (Folder 1) (Box 9)
        - (Folder 2) (Box 9)
          General
          (Includes "National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students Annual Report, 1962-1963" and "Newsweek," July 29, 1963)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 9)
        (Includes Carnegie Corporation of New York quarterly, January 1965, Volume XIII No. 1)
      - Committee on Equality of Opportunity, Material taken to Pittsburgh, January 23, 1965; Oct. 1964-Apr. 1965 (Box 9)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 9)
      - Take With-ACE-30, March 1965; Jan.-Mar. 1965 (Box 9)
        (Includes: "Committment to Expanding Opportunity: Proposals for Federal Action in Education," American Council on Education, 1965)
    - Committee on Leaders and Specialists, Aug. 1962-May 1963 (Box 9)
    - Fact Book on Higher Education (Box 9)
      - 1962, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 9)
      - Extra Sheets, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Office of Statistical Information and Research, Jul. 1962-Jun. 1963 (Box 9)
    - San Francisco Meeting, Fall 1964; Apr.-Oct. 1964 (Box 9)
  - American Security Council, 1962/1966; (4 folders) (Box 9)
  - ASCAP, 1947-1968 (Box 9)
  - American Studies (Box 9)
    - 1963-1967, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1963-64; 1964 (Box 9)
  - Association of American University Presses-Lexington, Kentucky, May 25, 1965; Mar.-May 1965 (Box 9)
  - American Universities Field Staff (Box 9)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - American Universities Field Staff (Box 10)
    - 1964-1967, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Special Meeting, April 24, 1966; Jul. 1965-Apr. 1966 (Box 10)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 10)
    - Sep. 1962-Aug. 1963 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 10)
    - Letters and reports, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 10)
  - American Yugoslavia Program, 1965-1968 (Box 10)
  - American Council on Education (Box 10)
    - Publications, 1961-1963 (Box 10)
    - Special Report on Federal Programs, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 10)
  - American Dance Theatre Company, Dec. 1965-Sep. 1966 (Box 10)
  - American Fletcher National Bank and Trust Company, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 10)
  - American History, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - American Indian Ethnohistoric Conference, Nov. 1964 (Box 10)
  - The American Legion, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
  - American Red Cross, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - American Scholars Exchange with Soviet Union (faculty), Sep. 1964-Apr. 1965 (Box 10)
  - American Security Council, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
  - An, general, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 10)
  - Anatomy-Physiology, 1963-1965; 1967; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - An, general, Jul. 1962-Jun. 1963 (Box 10)
  - Anders general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 10)
  - Animal Welfare Lab, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Arthur Anderson Report, 1965-1970; (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Arthur Anderson and Company (Box 11)
    - Report, Budget Procedures at IU, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Auditors, May 1965; 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Reports, Aug.-Sep. 1965 (Box 11)
    - 1965 (Box 11)
  - Andr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 11)
  - Andres Bello (Universidad Catolica), Venezuela, Oct. 1966-Oct. 1967 (Box 11)
  - Andres Bello (Catholic University, Caracas, Venezuela), 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Angel Mounds, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Animal Laboratories (Box 11)
    - Animal Farm near Girl's School proposed, 1966-1968 (Box 11)
    - Kent Farm, Apr.-Jul. 1967 (Box 11)
    - Director of Laboratory Animal Medicine, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
    - 1962-1968 (Box 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Ar, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 11)
  - Arbutus Material and Arbutus, miscellaneous, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Archaeology, Sep. 1966-Jun. 1968 (Box 11)
  - Agreements-Alcoa, for archaeology exploration, May-Jun. 1967 (Box 11)
  - Archaeology-Salamis Project, Mar. 1963-Jan. 1964 (Box 11)
  - Archaeology, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
  - Architecture-School of Urban Planning, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 11)
  - School of Architecture-Proposed, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - Arn, general, Jul.-Sep. 1962 (Box 11)
  - Archives, 1962-1968 (Box 12)
  - School of Architecture-Proposed, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
  - Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Archives of Traditional Music, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - Archives of Folk & Primitive Music, Trimester Report, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Archives of the Languages of the World (Box 12)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 12)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 12)
  - Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Trimester Report, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Archives of Traditional Music (Box 12)
    - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
    - Trimester Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
    - Trimester Reports, 1967; 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - May-Jun. 1965 (Box 12)
  - Argonne, 1963-1966 (Box 12)
  - Armed Services, 1961-1964; (4 folders) (Box 12)
  - Arn, general, 1963-1966; (4 folders) (Box 12)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1961-1963; (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - 1962-1968 (Box 12)
    - Annual Report, 1962-1963; 1962-1964 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 12)
    - 1963-1968, (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - Annual Report, 1963-1967; (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - College of Fine Arts, Departmental Report, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - As, general, 1962-1968 (Box 12)
  - Agreement-ASCAP, Jul. 1965-Mar. 1966 (Box 12)
  - Asian Studies Program, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 12)
  - Asian Studies, Aug. 1962-Jun. 1963 (Box 12)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 12)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - (including complementary programs: Aspen Music Festival, etc.), 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - Assembly Hall- (Box 12)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 12)
    - Controversy (folder contains relevant copied items from 1958-1960) (Box 12)
      - 1962-1968 (Box 12)
      - Petitions in support of construction, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Associated Colleges of the Midwest, Annual Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 13)
  - Associated Midwest Universities, (includes minutes), 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 13)
  - Associated Universities, Inc. (Box 13)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 13)
    - Organization and Objectives, 31 Dec. 1963 (Box 13)
  - Association (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
      - A, 1966-1968 (Box 13)
      - B-M, 1966-1968 (Box 13)
      - N-Z, 1966-1968 (Box 13)
      - A, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
      - B-Z, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
      - A, 1964-1965 (Box 13)
      - B-Z, 1964-1965 (Box 13)
      - A, 1963-1965 (Box 14)
      - B-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
      - A, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
      - B-Z, 1962-1964 (Box 14)
    - Aerospace Medical Association, Aug.-Sep. 1964 (Box 14)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 14)
      - 1965-1967, (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Programs (Box 14)
        - 1962-1966, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1966-1968 (Box 14)
    - American Association of Collegiate Registrars, 1962 (Box 14)
    - American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1966-1968 (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors, (1940 statement on academic freedom and tenure), 1967-1968 (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors, Compensation Survey, (faculty salaries), 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors, the Economic Status of the ProfessionsReport on the self-grading compensation survey, 1961-1962; Jul-Aug. 1962 (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Women, 1962-1965; (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Bankers Association, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Bankers Association-Research Council, 1 Apr. 1963 (Box 14)
    - American Bar Association, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
    - ACPRA (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 14)
      - District Conferences, 1965-1967 (Box 14)
      - Institute-Chicago, Ill., April 3-5, 1967; 1966-1967 (Box 14)
      - July 1966 (July 4-5-6-7), Jun.-Jul. 1966 (Box 14)
      - 1965 Conference, (July 4-8, 1965); Mar.-Aug. 1965 (Box 14)
      - National Meeting, (July 5-6-7-8, 1964); Feb.-Oct. 1964 (Box 14)